Dick Russell Papers MS277
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Pollution / health effects, circa 1992 -- 2000; MS277.000218; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Pollution / Animal effects - frogs, etc., 1996 -- 1999; MS277.000219; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 13)
- New technology, 1988 -- 1990; MS277.000220; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Military - chemical, biological, and other weapons, 1989 -- 1990; MS277.000221; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Hazardous waste, circa 1988 -- 1991; MS277.000222; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Corporations / Businesses - environment, 1988 -- 1991; MS277.000223; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Pollution, circa 1988 -- 1991; MS277.000224; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Info - how to write to congress, right-to-know laws, hazardous waste management and firms, 1988 September -- 1988 November; MS277.000225; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Chemical companies, 1990 January -- 1990 December; MS277.000226; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Toxics - Amicus, 1989 October -- 1989 December; MS277.000227; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Nuclear power (general), circa 1974 -- 1990; MS277.000228; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Waste Management Incorporated, 1984 -- 1991; MS277.000229; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Waste / Chemical companies, 1983 -- 1991; MS277.000230; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Toxics, jobs and the environment, 1988 December; MS277.000231; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 3)
- The United States military's toxic legacy, 1991 January; MS277.000232; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 4)
- "Home Warriors" article, 1989 -- 1993; MS277.000233; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 5)
  Scope and Contents
  contains cassette tape
- National Toxics Campaign (NTC) / Pew Twist, 1991 -- 1993; MS277.000234; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Environmental justice - Amicus, 1984 -- 1993; MS277.000235; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Grassroots people and groups, circa 1986 -- 1991; MS277.000236; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Lois Gibbs (Big 10 - grassroots material), 1992 -- 1994; MS277.000237; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 9)
- NTC, Citizen's Clearinghouse for Hazardous Wastes (CCHW), grassroots, 1985 -- 1990; MS277.000238; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Love Canal / Western New York, 1978 -- 1991; MS277.000239; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Lois Gibbs book, 1988 -- 1991; MS277.000240; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Jacksonville, 1982 -- 1991; MS277.000241; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Business and environment, 1991 July -- 1991 August; MS277.000242; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 5)
- NTC/ Environmental Health Network (EHN) environmental health report, 1991 June -- 1991 July; MS277.000243; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Student Environmental Action Coalition (SEAC) conference lecture, 1991 August -- 1991 September; MS277.000244; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Kentucky story, 1987 -- 1991; MS277.000245; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Citizens suits - the nation, 1986 -- 1989; MS277.000246; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Colorado environment / Anderson, circa 1985 -- 1996; MS277.000247; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Irene Gills / John O'Conner, 1995 -- 1999; MS277.000248; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Hugh Kaufman - Nebraska residents interviews and notes, 1987 -- 1991; MS277.000249; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Nuclear waste - military and high level, 1988 -- 1992; MS277.000250; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Hugh Kaufman - California nuclear dump (Hollywood), 1987 -- 1991; MS277.000251; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Nebraska background - general, 1986 -- 1990; MS277.000252; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Hugh Kaufman - interview notes, 1989 -- 1990; MS277.000253; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Nebraska / Kaufman nuclear waste, 1989 -- 1990; MS277.000254; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Hugh Kaufman - Texas case, 1990 -- 2000; MS277.000255; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 7)
- EPA - Reagan era, 1984 -- 1992; MS277.000256; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Hugh Kauffman - Nebraska 1988 -- 1990, MS277.000257; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Low-level radioactive waste (LLRW) compacts - United States (general), 1988 -- 1991; MS277.000258; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Nuclear waste regulation, safety and other nuclear power issues, 1988 -- 1991; MS277.000259; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Hugh Kaufman and Nebraska nuclear waste 1991, 1989 -- 1992; MS277.000260; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Hugh Kaufman - Emmelle, Alabama, 1982 -- 1992; MS277.000261; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Hugh Kaufman - Burford / Lavelle scandal, circa 1980 -- 1984; MS277.000262; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 14)
- EPA - Bush era, 1987 -- 1992; MS277.000263; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Nebraska, 1991 -- 1992; MS277.000264; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Hugh Kaufman - pre-Reagan, circa 1978 -- 1984; MS277.000265; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Hugh Kaufman - 1984 -- 1988, MS277.000266; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Browning-Ferris Industries (see also Nebraska and United States ecology files), 1987 -- 1992; MS277.000267; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 4)
- EPA Bush superfund (general), circa 1989 -- 1991; MS277.000268; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Hugh Kaufman Pennsylvania case 1991, 1990 -- 1991; MS277.000269; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Hugh Kaufman - Jacksonville, Arkansas, 1988 -- 1990; MS277.000270; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Hugh Kaufman - North Carolina / William Reilly scandal, 1989 -- 1991; MS277.000271; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Hugh Kaufman major cases - Bush era, 1988 -- 1989; MS277.000272; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 9)
- United States ecology / Bechtel, circa 1987 -- 1991; MS277.000273; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Hugh Kaufman, circa 2001 -- 2009; MS277.000274; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Toxics - waste problems and solutions, circa 1986 -- 1991; MS277.000275; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Hugh Kaufman - Chapter 1, outline, correspondence, 1991 -- 1992; MS277.000276; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Vernon incinerator, 1986 -- 1989; MS277.000277; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Kaye Kike / Emmelle, 1986 -- 1987; MS277.000278; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Toxics and race (general), 1986 -- 1988; MS277.000279; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Kettleman City, California, circa 1986 -- 1988; MS277.000280; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Lancer incineration, 1983 -- 1989; MS277.000281; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Boston Edison manuscript, 1978 -- 1981; MS277.000282; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Jacksonville and Technical Assistance Grant (TAG), circa 1988 -- 1990; MS277.000283; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Arkansas, circa 1988 -- 1989; MS277.000284; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Jacksonville, Arkansas, circa 1976 -- 1991; MS277.000285; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Calvert City (Lynn Ray Hill case), circa 1987 -- 1991; MS277.000286; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Kentucky - Calvert City, 1981 -- 1988; MS277.000287; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Mississippi River story (Greenpeace), circa 1983 -- 1988; MS277.000288; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Louisiana and Mississippi (toxics), 1983 -- 1988; MS277.000289; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Incineration article - Amicus, 1988 -- 1989; MS277.000290; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Greenpeace 1987, circa 1986 -- 1990; MS277.000291; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Berkshires - land trust story, 1982 -- 1989; MS277.000292; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Right-wing environmental activism, circa 1987 -- 1988; MS277.000293; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Nation professional corporation - environmental movement, 1988 -- 1989; MS277.000294; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Fair media / Environmental project, 1989 -- 1990; MS277.000295; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Media / Environment, 1988 -- 1990; MS277.000296; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Earth Day 1990, circa 1971 -- 1990; MS277.000297; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Wrench meetings, 1983 -- 1990; MS277.000298; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 11)